[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 16]
Tomorrow, I'll set up a magic circle under Lusitai.
And use Liu Shao's flesh
to refine the Blood Amulet.
I'm willing to help you
to protect the magic circle.
No one is allowed to go near Lusitai
for three days.
Yes.
No way.
Is it true that Immortal Luo Ge
is going to use your flesh to refine the Blood Amulet?
Yes.
Why?
Restoring the Four Seasons Monument is so important.
You are too weak to bear it.
It is said that I have the Power of the Sun.
The Four Seasons Monument was sealed by God of the Sun.
Of course I have to contribute.
To contribute with your life?
Exactly.
I only have one life.
Who would like to
risk their lives to bet?
Of course.
To bet on what?
To bet
that Luo Ge
is still that Lu Li who loves me,
and doesn't want me to die.
But...
what if he is really willing
to fill the Four Seasons Monument with you?
Liu Shao,
have you made up your mind?
The seven talisman pearls
are related to your soul.
If I said no,
would Immortal Palace give up
taking my blood
or would you give up
refining amulet with me?
Neither would Immortal Palace nor me.
Although I have the Power of the Sun,
I never hurt anyone.
Whether it's Immortal Palace or you
filling the monument
with my blood
is both a betrayal of me.
Yes.
It's me who betrayed you.
It's not Immortal Luo Ge who betrayed me,
but you,
the man standing in front of me.
Not only did you fail to keep your promise
to protect me for the rest of my life,
but you also
hurt me, betrayed me,
and used my blood to fill the monument.
Lu Li is the one who promised you, not me.
You are Lu Li.
There's no such a person in this world.
Then just tell me,
who is that affectionate Lu Li
who would cry, laugh,
and would sacrifice his life
because of a little obsession in his heart?
Even if he did exist,
he's long dead by now.
Now that Lu Li is dead,
I will keep my promise
to die with him.
I hope I can still
catch up with him in the other world
and still get to see
his beating
moon-shaped heart.
Lu Li...
Wait for me.
The restoration of the Four Seasons Monument has begun.
Looks like
those talisman pearls are working.
That's great.
What a good news.
Isn't this migic circle
being hosted by Immortal Luo Ge all the time?
Why did I just see him go back to Xiyin Mountain?
It can run on its own
without being hosted by others.
I'm leaving.
I'll go back to wash up
and go to bed.
The person who looks the same as Lu Li
is no longer the caring
and affectionate Lu Li.
It seemed that Lu Li
was really gone.
So you are the traitor.
I will tell you all this
with paper money from the human world
on the seventh day after your death.
Immortal?
What else
do you have to say now?
I just don't want you
to be seduced by this mortal woman.
So I destroyed her flesh
and left her divine spirit for you.
Even without her flesh,
you can still use her divine spirit to refine the Blood Amulet, right?
How can I make it
without her flesh?
You are still playing fool,
Xie Lingqi?
You can execute me
to test my innocence
if you still have doubts about me.
You have been wrapped in demon aura.
Why are you still in denial?
Take a good look at it.
You really think the Protection Spell you broke into is a Blood Amulet magic circle,
and you are still
on Lusitai?
Ge.
Didn't you say that this time
you could escort the spy of the Demons back to Litian Temple?
But why did you use the Star Teleportation spell
to bring General Xie here?
Immortal.
Immortal Master.
I...
I'm innocent.
From Protection Spell being damaged
to Ziji Shield being exploited
to Bone-Corroding Harp's demon voice
hitting the cracks of Four Seasons Monument straight on.
So,
Ao Hen knew where the Ziji Shield was,
and knew which part of the Four Seasons Monument was the weakest.
Exactly.
So I was sure
that she had colluded with someone here.
So I deliberately told everyone
that I would use Liu Shao's blood to refine the talisman pearl
to restore the Four Seasons Monument.
All I know is
that Liu Shao has agreed to use her flesh to refine the talisman pearl
in order to restore the Four Seasons Monument.
I did all these just to lure you out.
You have been wrapped in demon aura.
What else can you say?
I've been killing demons in the Three Realms,
so it's inevitable that I would be contaminated with some demonic aura.
You're right.
I really can't stand
Liu Shao
and hate her.
I admit it all.
But you have no right to say
that I colluded with the demon world and tried to destroy Immortal Palace
on the basis of this incident alone.
Immortal.
General Xie, as the guardian of the monument,
has been in the Immortal Palace for more than a thousand years.
He could not have waited until now
if he had already got a different intention.
Such a strong demon aura.
How many years have you colluded with the Demons?
It looks like
it has been more than ten years.
No.
I didn't.
Who is it
that you colluded with?
I don't know.
Your qualifications and cultivation are above mine.
Why would you...
Yeah!
I also want to know
why someone like you
could become the Master of the Palace Wuxie.
You did all this for such a trivial matter?
A trivial matter?
I, Xie Lingqi,
have been working hard for so long
to help the Three Realms of Immortal Palace.
I have participated in more than a thousand campaigns
and more than ten thousand
battles
to protect Immortal Palace's Regulation.
I've had more injuries
than I can count.
But in the end,
I couldn't even compare with that pompous
Shang Yurong.
And you.
I got this new scar
to protect you when Luo Ge was in retreat.
You haven't forgotten all that, have you?
All of you
are just staying out of this matter.
How many of you are like me
who fought hard on the blood-soaked battlefield
to get where I am now?
So someone used the resentment in your heart
to infuse the demon aura into your heart step by step.
I don't care why you colluded with him.
You'll be a prisoner of Immortal Palace
for the rest of your life.
Guards!
Yes.
Put Xie Lingqi in Bone Melting Pool
for eternity.
I'll go there by myself.
So, you and Luo Ge
set this all up together?
Hush.
You've been acting with Luo Ge
since the conferring ceremony.
Although Luo Ning said you were useless,
the person who set this up with Luo Ge
could never be useless.
Now you know
how important I am.
I didn't treat you unfairly.
I got a lot of energy cultivation pills from Luo Ge
for you.
Look at you.
You look much better.
That's because I was useful.
Not only could I help you make the talisman pearl,
but I could also be your bait.
Don't blame it all on Luo Ge.
You were not the only one he was cruel to.
He was more cruel to himself.
In order to experience hardships in the mortal world,
he sealed his five senses,
and even removed half of his heart
to fall into the mortal world.
He has suffered so much more
than you've done
in refining of Blood Amulet.
So tell me,
for a ruthless person like him,
is he good or evil?
All he gets is what he wants.
The tragic ending of Lu Li
is just a tribulation for him to become an Immortal.
Others,
even if they fell into hell for eternity,
they would still just be an insignificant detail
in this tribulation.
They can be ignored at any time.
Why?
You rushed back to check the injury of Miss Liu
after dealing with the matter of the spy, didn't you?
I'll go back first.
Liu Shao.
Can you take it
if I ask you to take two more talisman pearls?
Why should I do this?
After you trampled on my heart,
I still need to dedicate my body
to fulfill your honorable reputation
of guarding the Three Realms?
Do you ever feel guilty?
Yes, I do.
But I have to make my choice
since I have responsibility.
Sacrifice yourself then.
Sacrifice yourself to fill that Four Seasons Monument.
Why do you expect a mortal like me
to sacrifice my body, my mind
and even my life?
Why should I do this?
Sacrifice yourself then.
Sacrifice yourself to fill that Four Seasons Monument.
Why do you expect a mortal like me
to sacrifice my body, my mind,
and even my life?
As long as I'm here,
you will never come out,
even without the blood talisman pearl.
Ge,
The Four Seasons Monument hasn't been fully restored yet.
Why did you remove the magic circle?
Liu Shao has taken out four talisman pearls,
and restored more than half of the Four Seasons Monument.
She has done enough.
Since there's a chance to restore the Four Seasons Monument completely,
why did you give up?
Have you forgotten about
what was suppressed under the monument?
It was half of God of the Moonlight's heart.
Back then,
the Three Realms were in chaos,
and the demonic aura arises.
In order to protect the worlds,
the God of the Moonlights sealed the demonic aura by himself.
But unexpectedly,
that demonic aura has formed a mind and turned into an evil creature.
It controlled God of the Moonlight.
The God of the Sun had to kill him
and suppressed the corrupted half of his heart
under the Four Seasons Monument.
And you were born of the other pure part of his heart.
You should know what your mission is.
Now, the Four Seasons Monument is turbulent.
The demonic creature under the monument
could come out anytime to harm all beings.
Ge,
you can't miss any chance
to eliminate the hidden danger.
The best way to eliminate the hidden danger
is to become a God as soon as possible.
But I failed this woman during my tribulation.
If I used her once again as a stepping stone,
it would harm my morality
and be bad for me to become a God.
But,
she is a mortal after all.
A mortal is also a human being.
Moreover,
how could someone possessed by Sun Spirit
be an ordinary person?
Immortal Master,
listen to my advice.
Don't push her anymore.
What if she helps the Demons?
Ge,
do not forget
that so far she hasn't told us
about the origin of that demon string.
Greetings, Immortal Master.
You've been here for a while, right?
Yes.
What do you want from Immortal Palace?
I've always admired Immortal Palace.
I want to stay here to cultivate
and protect the Three Realms.
Was it out of kindness when
you saved the lower-level disciple of Immortal Palace
the other day?
Since I've been cultivating myself,
saving people is just an instinct of mine.
You were the disciple of Marquis Wuyang,
and senior of Lu Li.
You were deprived of direct discipleship because of Liu Shao,
so you hold a grudge against her.
The reason why you saved people in the immortal world
was just to
stay in Immortal Palace to take revenge on Liu Shao.
Am I right?
Immortal Master, I...
Take it.
Do you know what I gave you?
I don't think
I should ask you about it.
It is the Golden Pill that can improve your cultivation.
From today onwards,
I need you to go to Xiyin Mountain,
and protect Luo Ge for me.
Protect Immortal Luo Ge?
Are you willing to
see Liu Shao arouse Luo Ge's feelings,
and then they finally become a couple?
No, I'm not.
Fine.
Then I'm counting on you.
You're only allowed to stop them from being together.
Don't do anything stupid.
Otherwise, you will be punished.
Yes.
Liu Shao,
can you stop crying?
How many tears
have you shed today?
Even my leaves
are pickled by the salt in your tears.
Then why are you walking around in front of me?
I'm just worried about you.
There's nothing good about Immortal Palace.
It's not even as good as the Pearl Pavilion.
At least when I closed my eyes,
I would see Ling Xueyang smile at me.
You are right.
What's so good about here?
Everytime I opened my eyes,
I would see someone with the same face as Lu Li.
But every words he said
were like knives
that stabbed my heart.
I've figured it out.
Perhaps...
he's not Lu Li at all.
He's just a jerk who stole the appearance of Lu Li.
Liu Shao, did you notice that...
the immortals in Immortal Palace
always like to appear and disappear mysteriously?
I'll visit you later.
Yes.
I wonder what kind of Immortal
would always eavesdrop behind others.
Lu Li wouldn't do that.
Lu Li
used to call himself an Immortal.
But he was a liar.
We promised each other
that we would only be mortals for a lifetime,
instead of being immortals with loneliness of thousands of years.
I'm afraid I can't return the Bone-Corroding Harp to you
because it was connected by demon string.
Take this ice string zither as compensation.
You can learn this Great Tone and Six Senses Symphony first,
if you have time.
It can help you calm your mind down.
I can teach you if you have any questions.
So,
the reason why you gave me the zither
and music score
was just to make me forget about
my relationship with Lu Li.
It's your call if you want to keep that memory.
Okay.
I will forget.
I'll forget about everything since I met you at Immortal Palace,
and keep what you've forgotten
in my mind.
They are playing the zither together.
Interesting.
Then they are not far
from falling in love, right?
Where have I heard this song?
This is
the sound of the Brahma tree blossoming.
Brahma tree?
Was it Aquatic Demons
who repaired the Bone-Corroding Harp for you?
Yes.
Liu Shao, you're finally awake.
How did I fall asleep?
Wasn't I playing the zither with him?
You seem to have betrayed He Na just now.
Where is the Demon King in White?
It is Luo Ge from Xiyin Mountain.
Luo Ge?
I'll go meet him.
Don't you go out.
Lu Li?
I'm Luo Ge,
from Xiyin Mountain.
Luo Ge?
We Aquatic Demons live underwater
and don't ask about the outside world.
Immortal Luo Ge,
tell me why you're here.
I'm here
to ask you something.
Did you give this string
to Liu Shao?
Yes.
You created chaos in Immortal Palace
and caused many innocent deaths.
The Four Seasons Monument got unstable and the three worlds were in danger.
He Na,
You are unforgivable.
Fu.
Stop!
He Na, are you okay?
I'm fine.
The reason why you gave me ice string zither,
talked to me about the past,
and let my guard down,
was to get me to betray He Na.
I just need the truth.
The truth is he did give me the string.
But he did it to save me,
not to use me.
So,
you'd rather believe the words from a demon,
right?
If you were Lu Li,
you would believe him too.
Not only did he save me,
he also saved Lu Li,
again and again.
The demon string came from Demon King.
You can't deny this, can you?
Even if the matter was not related to you,
it was at least related to the demon world.
I'll give you one day
to find out the truth.
I've cast Protection Spell around your palace.
In one day,
no one
is allowed to leave.
In order to find out the truth,
you need to know
what happened that day at Lusitai.
Brahma tree,
if you dare to shake my mind,
don't blame me for ruining your foundation.
That's what happened.
When I was fixing the Four Seasons Monument,
I felt that the string were controled by others,
instead of me.
That's why
the Immortal Palace Boundary was destroyed,
and demons made a lot of mess there.
Lu Li protected us.
But I failed to protect him.
I didn't expect
this Immortal
looks exactly like Lu Li.
He is Lu Li.
He has just forgetten the past.
Or maybe,
Lu Li
is an insignificant existence
in his thousand-year life,
just like dust,
can be slapped away easily.
Immortal Luo Ge
is famous for being heartless.
But I don't understand.
Since Immortal Luo Ge is heartless,
why would he turn into that sentimental Lu Li
when he came to the mortal world
to overcome his tribulation?
Liu Shao.
Sometimes,
persistence
may only hurt you.
I'm not persistent.
All I care about
is Lu Li,
not this heartless Luo Ge.
Now,
he forced you to look for the truth.
Do you have any clues?
We can only declare that
we found Immortal Ze Shui's hair.
We can't  tell him
that our spiritual veins can be replaced.
If something happens to Bone-Corroding Harp again,
they will come back to us.
You are powerful enough.
But I can't take it any more.
One more extraction might
take my life.
I didn't recall anything yet.
Let me think about it.
Do you have any wine?
Of course.
I'll ask someone to give it to you.
Prove it.
Prove what?
Prove that you're no longer Lu Li, a mortal.
It was under this tree
that day,
where Lu Li told me those sincere words after he was drunk,
and made me a promise for a lifetime.
Madam,
you once bloomed ten thousand flowers
to witness it for us, right?
What are you doing?
Now you are even interfering with
the feeling of a tree?
It was too noisy.
You are afraid to face it,
or drink this wine.
♫In the sea of clouds, I looked at the reflection of the moon in the water♫
You're afraid that after drinking it,
you would become Lu Li again.
♫I kept waiting and arched my palms into a circle♫
Lu Li no longer exists.
♫The reflection gradually reminded me of our first meeting♫
Prove it to me then.
Even if you are an Immortal,
♫I can no longer tell the difference between wind and rain♫
you can't change the fact
that you have stepped on my sincere heart
on your way
to become an Immortal.
♫Even if I get the volley sword♫
Luo Ge.
♫I can't forget you♫
You owe me.
♫Our destiny has been sealed long ago♫
♫I have no other choice♫
♫Why have you been so far away from me every time♫
♫For billions of years♫
♫Can I use your hands to warm up the world again?♫
♫A few hasty nights♫
I told you Lu Li no longer exists.
I'm still Luo Ge.
♫Too many intertwined oaths and lies♫
Nothing has changed.
♫Have shattered my dreams♫
♫Who would like to take a broken willow branch♫
♫And watch the moon alone in the blue sky♫
♫The remaining flowers in the mirror reflect the moon in the water♫
Yes,
Lu Li no longer exists.
♫We can't live up to such a good time♫
♫Recalling the unforgettable glance at the beginning♫
♫I realized that it was a thousand years ago♫
♫Is this bad luck, or good luck?♫
So...
the face that looked exactly like Lu Li,
♫He said that responsibility and love are difficult to balance♫
and the way he looked at me once in a while,
♫He had no choice but to leave me♫
were all faked.
♫The past has passed, do not linger♫
Even if he has Lu Li's heart,
♫My love for you is still so strong♫
he's not Lu Li.
♫Too many intertwined oaths and lies♫
Lu Li
is really gone.
♫Have shattered my dreams♫
♫Who would like to take a broken willow branch♫
♫And watch the moon alone in the blue sky♫
What's wrong?
Why do you have that look on your face?
So it was you behind
all those incidents on Lusitai.
You had planed everything
when you gave up the spirit vein.
Do you think I did anything wrong?
Do you still think you did the right thing?
Do you know how many people have died
in that battle?
Of course I know.
Even the great demon Ao Hen,
who was your only opponent in the demon world,
has died over there.
Isn't it good for us
to rule the entire demon world?
So what?
Can we set our feet on shore?
So...
so we need to break the curse.
But have you ever thought about
what will happen
if that evil creature under Four Seasons Monument is released?
I thought it through.
It might cause chaos to the three worlds,
or bring trouble to all living beings.
But so what?
As long as we break the curse
to free the Aquatic Demons,
so that we can walk freely
under the sun,
anything
is worth the price.
As the Demon King,
no one wants to relieve the suffering of my people more than I do.
But it shouldn't
be based on other people's suffering.
No.
You're wrong.
As long as our people are no longer in pain,
then
any sacrifice
is worth it,
including my life
and
your life.
But did those sacrifices
get you what you wanted?
Or was it for a greater sacrifice of our people?
If Immortal Luo Ge get angry,
It will be a slaughter inside this palace.
How can we stop him if that happens?
Fine.
Since you think what I did was wrong,
I'll take the responsibility.
I do not judge the right or wrong of what you do.
Fu,
you've suffered so much.
It's me who failed to protect you.
Madam,
do you remember
he told me...
I said
that lifetime is long.
What if I can't afford you?
He said to me,
I'll sell myself to you.
I'll sell myself to you
-for one tael of silver. -One tael of silver.
-Okay? -Okay?
One tael of silver.